Guide to the President's Office General Subject and Correspondence Files 1910-1974
Oregon State University Libraries, Special Collections and Archives Research Center
- Oregon State College/University, 1910-1974; Series 2
  - Research Centers and Institutes
    - Institute of Nuclear Science and Engineering (Reel-folder 171.617)
    - Instructional Resources and Materials Center (Reel-folder 171.618)
    - International Plant Protection Center (Reel-folder 171.619)
    - Marine Science Center (Reel-folder 171.620)
    - Marine Science Center - Georgia Pacific Tideland (Reel-folder 171.621)
    - Nutritional Research Institute (Reel-folder 171.622)
    - Remote Sensing Center (Reel-folder 171.623)
    - Transportation Research Institute (Reel-folder 171.624)
    - USDCF Engineering Lab - Newport (MSB) (Reel-folder 171.625)
    - Water Resource Research Institute (Reel-folder 171.626)
  - Student Life
    Reel-Folder numbers starting with 47 added during data entry, as no numbers were assigned in container list.
    - Alumni Association (Reel-folder 47.01)
    - Associated Students (Reel-folder 47.02)
    - Cooperative Association - Bookstore (1 of 2) (Reel-folder 173.656)
    - Cooperative Association - Bookstore (2 of 2) (Reel-folder 174.656)
    - Dad's Club (Reel-folder 174.657)
    - Dean of Men (Reel-folder 174.658)
    - Dean of Women (Reel-folder 174.659)
    - Educational Activities (Reel-folder 174.660)
    - Educational Funds (Reel-folder 47.03)
    - General (Reel-folder 174.665)
    - Health Service (Reel-folder 174.666)
    - Intercollegiate Athletics (Reel-folder 47.04)
    - Interfraternity Council - General (Reel-folder 174.676)
    - Living Groups (Reel-folder 47.05)
    - Mother's Club (Reel-folder 175.693)
    - OSU Federation (Reel-folder 175.694)
    - Prizes and Awards - Agricultural Cooperative Council of Oregon (Reel-folder 175.695)
    - Prices and Awards - General (Reel-folder 175.696)
    - Phi Sigma Award (Reel-folder 175.697)
    - Students - Employment (Reel-folder 175.698)
    - Student Field Trips (Reel-folder 175.699)
    - Foreign Student Counselor (Reel-folder 175.700)
    - Foreign Student Counselor - News Bulletin (Reel-folder 175.701)
    - Students - General (Reel-folder 175.702)
    - Students - Prospective (Reel-folder 175.703)
    - Student Rights (1 of 2) (Reel-folder 175.704)
    - Students Rights (2 of 2) (Reel-folder 176.704)
- Oregon State Board/System of Higher Education, 1940-1972; Series 3
  Series 3 features 14 Sub-Series that document the University’s involvement with the Oregon State Board and System of Higher Education. This involvement includes: Committees, such as the Academic Affairs and Building Committee; the Extension Division; general files on subjects such as the University of Oregon and Biennial Reports; General materials associated with the Oregon State System of Higher Education; institutions, such as Portland State College, Eastern Oregon State College (Eastern Oregon University), and Linn-Benton Community College; and the KOAC TV and Radio.
  - Committees
    - Academic Affairs, 1963-1968 (Reel-folder 107.576)
    - Advisory Council on Teacher Education (Anderson Report) (Reel-folder 107.577)
    - Agricultural Extension Service and Experiment Stations (Reel-folder 107.578)
    - Building Committee (1 of 2), 1963-1964 (Reel-folder 107.579)
    - Building Committee (2 of 2), 1963-1964 (Reel-folder 108.579)
    - Curricula Committee, 1940-1961 (Reel-folder 108.580)
    - Finance Committee, 1963-1964 (Reel-folder 108.581)
    - General Extension Division Policies (Reel-folder 108.582)
    - Interinstitutional Committee on Public Relations Colleges for Oregon's Future (1 of 2), 1960 (Reel-folder 108.583)
    - Interinstitutional Committee on Public Relations Colleges for Oregon's Future (2 of 2), 1960-1961 (Reel-folder 108.584)
    - Interinstitutional Dormitory Committee (1 of 2), 1952-1960 (Reel-folder 108.585)
    - Interinstitutional Dormitory Committee, 1960-1967 (Reel-folder 108.586)
    - Interinstitutional Fee, 1960-1967 (Reel-folder 108.587)
    - Interinstitutional Placement Testing (Reel-folder 108.588)
    - Interinstitutional Research Committee (Reel-folder 108.589)
    - Interinstitutional Admissions (1 of 2), 1955-1960 (Reel-folder 108.590)
    - Interinstitutional Admissions (2 of 2), 1955-1960 (Reel-folder 109.590)
    - Interinstitutional Committee - General, 1967 (Reel-folder 109.591)
    - Interinstitutional Fee Committee, 1952-1960 (Reel-folder 109.592)
    - Interinstitutional Television Communications, 1952-1960 (Reel-folder 109.593)
    - Committee Salaries (Reel-folder 109.594)
    - Public Relations (Reel-folder 109.595)
  - Comptroller, 1950-1970 (Reel-folder 109.596)
  - Continuing Education - General, 1965-1967 (Reel-folder 109.597)
  - Executive Council - Committees, 1942-1961 (Reel-folder 109.598)
  - High School College Relations Committee, 1951-1961 (Reel-folder 109.599)
  - Extension Division
    - Educational TV - General (1 of 2), 1960-1965 (Reel-folder 109.600)
    - Educational TV - General (2 of 2), 1965-1967 (Reel-folder 109.601)
    - KOAC - Retainer Agreement, 1947 (Reel-folder 109.602)
    - KOAC - TV - Departmental Suggestions for Interinstitutional use of TV (Reel-folder 110.603)
    - KOAC - Engineering (formerly Operations and Maintenance) (Reel-folder 110.604)
    - KOAC - License and Ownership (Reel-folder 110.605)
    - Portland Extension Center (Reel-folder 110.606)
    - Visual Instruction (Reel-folder 110.607)
    - Information Division, 1950 (Reel-folder 110.608)
    - Community Colleges - General, 1967 (Reel-folder 110.609)
    - Elementary Education, 1953 (Reel-folder 110.610)
  - Institutions - Portland State College, 1960-1968 (Reel-folder 110.611)
  - Institutions - University of Oregon, 1960 (Reel-folder 110.612)
  - Institutional Executives Meetings, 1966-1969 (Reel-folder 110.613)
  - Institutional Executives - Meetings, Notices, 1969-1970 (Reel-folder 110.614)
  - Committees - Library Committee (Reel-folder 110.615)
  - Interinstitutional Committees - Merit Awards (Reel-folder 110.616)
  - Interinstitutional Committees - to study Student-Teacher Ratios (Reel-folder 110.617)
  - General
    Reel-Folder numbers starting with 3 added during data entry, as no numbers were assigned in container list.
    - Chancellor (1 of 2), 1962-1968 (Reel-folder 110.618)
    - Chancellor (2 of 2) (Reel-folder 110.619)
    - Chancellor's Guidelines (Reel-folder 110.620)
    - Executive Meetings (Reel-folder 3.01)
    - Management Improvement, 1968 (Reel-folder 111.626)
    - Meetings, Notices of, 1964-1967 (Reel-folder 111.627)
    - Policies and Procedures - Resolutions and History (Reel-folder 111.628)
    - Office of Institutional Research, 1968
    - Revision of Administrative Code, 1951-1960 (Reel-folder 112.630)
  - Letters - Telegrams - Messages - Campus Disturbance (Reel-folder 112.631)
  - University of Oregon, 1967 (Reel-folder 112.632)
  - Biennial Reports to the President, 1968-1970 (Reel-folder 112.633)
  - Oregon State College Foundation (Reel-folder 113.634)
  - Building Committee, 1964-1965 (Reel-folder 130.2297)
  - General
    - Executive's Meeting - Minutes, 1963 (Reel-folder 130.2300)
    - Executive's Meetings Notices - Agendas, 1965 (Reel-folder 130.2301)
    - Executive's Meetings - Notices - Minutes, 1955-1962 (Reel-folder 130.2302)
    - Executive's Meeting - Notices - Agendas, 1963-1964 (Reel-folder 130.2303)
    - Executives Meetings - Notices - Minutes, 1962-1963 (Reel-folder 130.2304)
    - Meetings, Notices of (1 of 2), 1958-1964 (Reel-folder 130.2305)
    - Meetings, Notices of (2 of 2), 1948-1958 (Reel-folder 130.2306)
    - Members - Correspondence with, 1951-1966 (Reel-folder 130.2307)
    - Members - Correspondence (Reel-folder 130.2308)
    - Members - Correspondence, 1947 and prior (Reel-folder 130.2309)
    - Secretary - Correspondence, 1948 and prior (Reel-folder 130.2310)
    - Obligation Bond Measure (Reel-folder 130.2311)
  - Committees
    - Alumni General Promotion Committee (Reel-folder 130.2312)
    - Advisory Committee on Teacher Education - Survey (Anderson Report) No. 1 (Reel-folder 130.2313)
    - Building Committee (1 of 4), 1962-1963 (Reel-folder 130.2314)
    - Building Committee (2 of 4), 1961-1962 (Reel-folder 130.2315)
    - Building Committee (3 of 4), 1961-1962 (Reel-folder 131.2315)
    - Building Committee (4 of 4), 1960-1961 (Reel-folder 131.2316)
  - Survey of Teacher Education in Oregon - Oregon State (2 books) (Reel-folder 131.2317)
  - Committees
    - Building Committee (1 of 2), 1957-1959 (Reel-folder 131.2318)
    - Building Committee (2 of 2), 1940-1957 (Reel-folder 131.2319)
    - Cost of Milk Study Investigation - Folder I, 1951 (Reel-folder 131.2320)
    - Curricula Committee - The Aim of Oregon State College (Reel-folder 131.2321)
    - Finance Committee (1 of 3), 1957-1962 (Reel-folder 131.2324)
    - Finance Committee (2 of 3), 1950-1957 (Reel-folder 131.2325)
    - Finance Committee (3 of 3), 1940-1950 (Reel-folder 131.2326)
    - Unified Administration Committee (Reel-folder 131.2327)
  - Oregon State System of Higher Education - General
    - Budget Director, 1946-1952 (Reel-folder 131.2328)
    - Chancellor, 1947-1948 (Reel-folder 131.2329)
    - Chancellor - Paul C. Packer (Reel-folder 131.2330)
    - Chancellor, 1946-1947 (Reel-folder 131.2331)
    - Chancellor - Meetings (Reel-folder 131.2333)
    - Chancellor - Regionalism (Reel-folder 131.2334)
    - Chancellor - A Ten-Year Look Ahead (Reel-folder 131.2335)
    - Chancellor - Reports to Governor (Reel-folder 131.2336)
    - Vice Chancellor (Reel-folder 131.2337)
    - Comptroller (Reel-folder 131.2338)
    - Summer Sessions, 1960-1964 (Reel-folder 131.2339)
    - State Board Reports (Radio and TV) (Reel-folder 131.2340)
  - Executive Council, 1948-1949 (Reel-folder 131.2341)
  - Executive Council, 1947 and prior (Reel-folder 131.2342)
  - Executive Council - Committees - Miscellaneous (Reel-folder 131.2343)
  - Committees
    - Committee to Study Relationships between General Extension Division and Other Institutions (Reel-folder 131.2345)
    - Cost of Milk Study Investigation - Folder II, 1951 (Reel-folder 131.2346)
    - Faculty Handbook (Reel-folder 131.2347)
    - Finance Committee - General Obligation Bond Issue of, 1951-1957 (Reel-folder 131.2348)
    - Interinstitutional Committee - Master's Degree in Education for Secondary Teachers at Oregon Colleges of Education, 1956-1957 (Reel-folder 131.2349)
    - Interinstitutional Committee - State and National Services (Reel-folder 131.2350)
    - Interinstitutional Curriculum (Reel-folder 131.2351)
    - Interinstitutional Dormitory Committee, 1946-1952 (Reel-folder 131.2352)
  - Extension Division
    - High School-College Relations Committee (Reel-folder 131.2354)
    - Other Colleges (Reel-folder 131.2355)
    - Portland State Extension Center (Merger of Vanport and Portland Extension Center) (Reel-folder 131.2356)
    - Summer Sessions, 1946-1948 (Reel-folder 131.2357)
    - Vanport Extension Center, merged with Portland State Extension Center, 1952 (Reel-folder 131.2358)
    - Vanport Extension Center (Reel-folder 131.2359)
    - Visual Aids (Reel-folder 131.2360)
  - Research - General (1 of 2) (Reel-folder 131.2361)
  - Research - General (2 of 2) (Reel-folder 132.2361)
  - Extension Division
    - General (1 of 4), 1958 (Reel-folder 132.2362)
    - General (2 of 4), 1950-1958 (Reel-folder 132.2363)
    - General (3 of 4), 1947-1957 (Reel-folder 132.2364)
    - General (4 of 4), 1944-1948 (Reel-folder 132.2365)
  - Graduate Division, 1940-1946 (Reel-folder 132.2366)
  - Information Division (Reel-folder 132.2367)
  - Institutions
    - Elementary Education, 1951-1953 (Reel-folder 132.2368)
    - Portland State College (1 of 2) (Reel-folder 132.2369)
    - Portland State College (2 of 2) (Reel-folder 132.2370)
    - Colleges of Education - Southern Oregon State College - Education (Reel-folder 132.2371)
  - Extension Division
    - KOAC - FCC and Educational Television, 1950-1953 (Reel-folder 132.2374)
    - Educational Television Material (Reel-folder 132.2375)
    - KOAC - Operation and Management, 1945 (Reel-folder 132.2377)
    - Possible Sale (Reel-folder 132.2380)
    - KOAC - Radio Advisory Council (Reel-folder 132.2381)
    - KOAC - General (Reel-folder 132.2382)
    - KOAC - General, 1947 and prior (Reel-folder 132.2383)
    - KOAC - TV - Curricula, 1957-1961 (Reel-folder 132.2384)
    - KOAC - TV - General, 1959-1960 (Reel-folder 132.2385)
  - Portland Graduate Center, 1966 (Reel-folder 132.2386)
  - Chancellor - Warren King and Associates (Reel-folder 176.705)
  - Committees - Constitution of the Interinstitutional Faculty Senate (Reel-folder 176.706)
  - Coordinating Council for Graduate Study (Reel-folder 176.707)
  - Educational Media Council (Reel-folder 176.708)
  - Interinstitutional Admissions (Reel-folder 176.709)
  - Interinstitutional Committee on Public Relations - College for Oregon's Future (Reel-folder 176.710)
  - Interinstitutional Fee (Reel-folder 176.711)
  - Interinstitutional Television (Reel-folder 176.712)
  - Interinstitutional Committee - General (Reel-folder 176.713)
  - High School - College Relations Committee (Reel-folder 176.714)
  - Comptroller (Reel-folder 176.715)
  - Division of Continuing Education - Concurrent Enrollment (Reel-folder 176.716)
  - General (Reel-folder 176.717)
  - General - Chancellor (Reel-folder 176.718)
  - General - Correspondence (Reel-folder 176.719)
  - Committees - Curricula Committee (Reel-folder 176.720)
  - Management Improvement (Reel-folder 176.721)
  - General - Operation Community Feedback (Reel-folder 176.722)
  - General - Revision of Administrative Code (Reel-folder 176.723)
  - General - Summer Session (Reel-folder 176.724)
  - Institutions
    - Oregon Technical Institute (Reel-folder 176.725)
    - Portland State College (Reel-folder 176.726)
    - Southern Oregon State College (Reel-folder 176.727)
    - University of Oregon (Reel-folder 176.728)
    - University of Oregon Dental School (Reel-folder 176.729)
    - University of Oregon Medical School (Reel-folder 176.730)
    - Linn-Benton Community College (Reel-folder 176.731)
    - Community College (Reel-folder 176.732)
    - Eastern Oregon State College (Reel-folder 176.733)
    - Oregon College of Education (Reel-folder 176.734)
  - Interinstitutional Committee of Classified and Unclassified Positions (Reel-folder 176.736)
  - KOAC TV and Radio
    - Educational TV - General (Reel-folder 176.737)
    - KOAC TV Budget (1 of 2) (Reel-folder 176.738)
    - KOAC TV Budget (2 of 2) (Reel-folder 177.738)
    - KOAC TV Cu rricula (Reel-folder 177.739)
    - KOAC Radio - General (Reel-folder 177.740)
    - KOAC-FEC - Educational Television (Reel-folder 177.741)
    - KOAP-TV Channel 10, Portland (Reel-folder 177.742)
  - Members - Correspondence with (Reel-folder 177.743)
  - Vice Chancellor for Academic Affairs (Reel-folder 177.744)
  - Vice Chancellor for Administration (1 of 2), 1967-1971 (Reel-folder 177.745)
  - Vice Chancellor for Administration (2 of 2), 1972 (Reel-folder 177.746)
  - Vice Chancellor for Facilities Planning (Reel-folder 177.747)